<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Filtered - Dark Reading</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/rss.xml</link><description>Filtered Dark Reading entries for Arcadia</description><item><title>AWS Enhances Cloud Security With Better Visibility Features</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud-security/aws-enhances-cloud-security-better-visibility</link><description>At this week's re:Inforce 2025 conference, the cloud giant introduced new capabilities to several core security products to provide customers with better visibility and more context on potential threats.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 01:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackers Post Dozens of Malicious Copycat Repos to GitHub</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/threat-intelligence/dozens-malicious-copycat-repos-github</link><description>As package registries find better ways to combat cyberattacks, threat actors are finding other methods for spreading their malware to developers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serpentine#Cloud Uses Cloudflare Tunnels in Sneak Attacks</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud-security/serpentinecloud-cloudflare-tunnels-sneak-attacks</link><description>An unidentified threat actor is using .lnk Windows shortcut files in a series of sophisticated attacks utilizing in-memory code execution and living-off-the-land cyberattack strategies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Post Staffer Emails Targeted in Cyber Breach</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/vulnerabilities-threats/washington-post-staffer-emails-targeted-cyber-breach</link><description>Journalists' Microsoft accounts were breached, which would have given attackers access to emails of staff reporters covering national security, economic policy, and China.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 19:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Water Curse' Targets Infosec Pros via Poisoned GitHub Repositories</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/cyberattacks-data-breaches/water-curse-targets-cybersecurity-pros-github-repos</link><description>The emerging threat group attacks the supply chain via weaponized repositories posing as legitimate pen-testing suites and other tools that are poisoned with malware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Threat Actor Abuses TeamFiltration for Entra ID Account Takeovers</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/cloud-security/threat-actor-teamfiltration-entra-id-attacks</link><description>Researchers discovered a large-scale campaign using the open source penetration-testing framework that has targeted more than 80,000 Microsoft accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 15:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers Detail Zero-Click Copilot Exploit 'EchoLeak'</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/application-security/researchers-detail-zero-click-copilot-exploit-echoleak</link><description>Researchers at Aim Security disclosed a Microsoft Copilot vulnerability of critical severity this week that could have enabled sensitive data exfiltration via prompt injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 20:49:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>