<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Filtered - Hacker News</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/rss.xml</link><description>Hacker News alerts filtered for Arcadia-relevant products and threats</description><item><title>Hackers Target Over 70 Microsoft Exchange Servers to Steal Credentials via Keyloggers</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hackers-target-65-microsoft-exchange.html</link><description>Unidentified threat actors have been observed targeting publicly exposed Microsoft Exchange servers to inject malicious code into the login pages that harvest their credentials.
Positive Technologies, in a new analysis published last week, said it identified two different kinds of keylogger code written in JavaScript on the Outlook login page -

Those that save collected data to a local file</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:56:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>XDigo Malware Exploits Windows LNK Flaw in Eastern European Government Attacks</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/xdigo-malware-exploits-windows-lnk-flaw.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a Go-based malware called XDigo that has been used in attacks targeting Eastern European governmental entities in March 2025.
The attack chains are said to have leveraged a collection of Windows shortcut (LNK) files as part of a multi-stage procedure to deploy the malware, French cybersecurity company HarfangLab said.
XDSpy is the name assigned to a cyber</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:42:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>200+ Trojanized GitHub Repositories Found in Campaign Targeting Gamers and Developers</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/67-trojanized-github-repositories-found.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new campaign in which the threat actors have published more than 67 GitHub repositories that claim to offer Python-based hacking tools, but deliver trojanized payloads instead.
The activity, codenamed Banana Squad by ReversingLabs, is assessed to be a continuation of a rogue Python campaign that was identified in 2023 as targeting the Python Package</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:11:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Secure Vibe Coding: The Complete New Guide</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/secure-vibe-coding-complete-new-guide.html</link><description>DALL-E for coders? That’s the promise behind vibe coding, a term describing the use of natural language to create software. While this ushers in a new era of AI-generated code, it introduces "silent killer" vulnerabilities: exploitable flaws that evade traditional security tools despite perfect test performance.
A detailed analysis of secure vibe coding practices is available here.
TL;DR: Secure</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:55:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Russian APT29 Exploits Gmail App Passwords to Bypass 2FA in Targeted Phishing Campaign</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/russian-apt29-exploits-gmail-app.html</link><description>Threat actors with suspected ties to Russia have been observed taking advantage of a Google account feature called application specific passwords (or app passwords) as part of a novel social engineering tactic designed to gain access to victims' emails.
Details of the highly targeted campaign were disclosed by Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) and the Citizen Lab, stating the activity</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:36:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>New Linux Flaws Enable Full Root Access via PAM and Udisks Across Major Distributions</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/new-linux-flaws-enable-full-root-access.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered two local privilege escalation (LPE) flaws that could be exploited to gain root privileges on machines running major Linux distributions.
The vulnerabilities, discovered by Qualys, are listed below -

CVE-2025-6018 - LPE from unprivileged to allow_active in SUSE 15's Pluggable Authentication Modules (PAM)
CVE-2025-6019 - LPE from allow_active to root in</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 09:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>1,500+ Minecraft Players Infected by Java Malware Masquerading as Game Mods on GitHub</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/1500-minecraft-players-infected-by-java.html</link><description>A new multi-stage malware campaign is targeting Minecraft users with a Java-based malware that employs a distribution-as-service (DaaS) offering called Stargazers Ghost Network.
"The campaigns resulted in a multi-stage attack chain targeting Minecraft users specifically," Check Point researchers Jaromír Hořejší and Antonis Terefos said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
"The malware was</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 19:48:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Water Curse Employs 76 GitHub Accounts to Deliver Multi-Stage Malware Campaign</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/water-curse-hijacks-76-github-accounts.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers have exposed a previously unknown threat actor known as Water Curse that relies on weaponized GitHub repositories to deliver multi-stage malware.
"The malware enables data exfiltration (including credentials, browser data, and session tokens), remote access, and long-term persistence on infected systems," Trend Micro researchers Jovit Samaniego, Aira Marcelo, Mohamed</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:17:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Chrome Zero-Day CVE-2025-2783 Exploited by TaxOff to Deploy Trinper Backdoor</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/google-chrome-zero-day-cve-2025-2783.html</link><description>A now-patched security flaw in Google Chrome was exploited as a zero-day by a threat actor known as TaxOff to deploy a backdoor codenamed Trinper.
The attack, observed in mid-March 2025 by Positive Technologies, involved the use of a sandbox escape vulnerability tracked as CVE-2025-2783 (CVSS score: 8.3).
Google addressed the flaw later that month after Kaspersky reported in-the-wild</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:46:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>Hard-Coded 'b' Password in Sitecore XP Sparks Major RCE Risk in Enterprise Deployments</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/hard-coded-b-password-in-sitecore-xp.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed three security flaws in the popular Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) that could be chained to achieve pre-authenticated remote code execution.
Sitecore Experience Platform is an enterprise-oriented software that provides users with tools for content management, digital marketing, and analytics and reports.
The list of vulnerabilities is as follows -</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:03:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>⚡ Weekly Recap: iPhone Spyware, Microsoft 0-Day, TokenBreak Hack, AI Data Leaks and More</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/weekly-recap-iphone-spyware-microsoft-0.html</link><description>Some of the biggest security problems start quietly. No alerts. No warnings. Just small actions that seem normal but aren't. Attackers now know how to stay hidden by blending in, and that makes it hard to tell when something’s wrong.
This week’s stories aren’t just about what was attacked—but how easily it happened. If we’re only looking for the obvious signs, what are we missing right in front</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:59:00 +0530</pubDate></item><item><title>PyPI, npm, and AI Tools Exploited in Malware Surge Targeting DevOps and Cloud Environments</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2025/06/malicious-pypi-package-masquerades-as.html</link><description>Cybersecurity researchers from&amp;nbsp;SafeDep and Veracode detailed a number of malware-laced npm packages that are designed to execute remote code and download additional payloads.
The packages in question are listed below -

eslint-config-airbnb-compat (676 Downloads)
ts-runtime-compat-check (1,588 Downloads)
solders (983 Downloads)
@mediawave/lib (386 Downloads)

All the identified npm</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 12:15:00 +0530</pubDate></item></channel></rss>