<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Filtered - Krebs on Security</title><link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/feed/</link><description>Filtered Krebs on Security entries for Arcadia</description><item><title>Patch Tuesday, June 2025 Edition</title><link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/06/patch-tuesday-june-2025-edition/</link><description>Microsoft today released security updates to fix at least 67 vulnerabilities in its Windows operating systems and software. Redmond warns that one of the flaws is already under active attack, and that software blueprints showing how to exploit a pervasive Windows bug patched this month are now public.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Breachforums Boss to Pay $700k in Healthcare Breach</title><link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/breachforums-boss-to-pay-700k-in-healthcare-breach/</link><description>In what experts are calling a novel legal outcome, the 22-year-old former administrator of the cybercrime community Breachforums will forfeit nearly $700,000 to settle a civil lawsuit from a health insurance company whose customer data was posted for sale on the forum in 2023. Conor Brian Fitzpatrick, a.k.a. "Pompompurin," is slated for resentencing next month after pleading guilty to access device fraud and possession of child sexual abuse material (CSAM).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Patch Tuesday, May 2025 Edition</title><link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2025/05/patch-tuesday-may-2025-edition/</link><description>Microsoft on Tuesday released software updates to fix at least 70 vulnerabilities in Windows and related products, including five zero-day flaws that are already seeing active exploitation. Adding to the sense of urgency with this month's patch batch from Redmond are fixes for two other weaknesses that now have public proof-of-concept exploits available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>